HUNG CHE CHEN



437-999-4732



https://www.linkedin.com/in/hung-che-chen/



hung.che.chen8@gmail.com



https://github.com/jer12182002?tab=repositories

EXPERIENCE

Programmer Analyst (Co-op)

Toronto Transit Commission(TTC)



09/2017 - 01/2018



Toronto, Ontario

Public Transportation Service

- Designed, developed, tested, deployed, maintained in Access SQL and VBA, and document solutions for challenging problems with robust, scalable, reusable, efficient, production-quality software.
- Maintained, redesigned, enhanced department websites in Javascript, CSS, and HTML by analyzing requirements.
- Provided new users guick development the proficiency reference they require in the use the department computer applications by developing on-line training modules.
- Provided professional analytic report for engineers to reduce wheels etching rate by calculating and creating weekly wheels etching ration statistical report with pivot table features.
- Provided excellent communication skills and agile methodology to clients to fulfill the needs.
- Assists user and operate areas in implementing and supporting systems including system installation, training and troubleshooting.
- Keeps equipment operational by calling for repairs; following manufacturer's instructions and established procedures; evaluating new equipment.

International Sales/Accounting Assistant

Powagrip Co. Ltd.



07/2014 - 08/2016



Tanzi Dist., Taiwan

International Trading Business

- Slashed payroll/benefits administration costs 30% by negotiating pricing and fees, while ensuring the continuation and enhancements.
- Increase number of clients by analyzing the business field.
- Reduced company advertisement cost 60% by creating company website and Poster design.
- Reduced administration fee by maintaining items by ERP system. Enhanced goods quality and satisfied clients by shipment arrangement.
- Prepared proposal with identifying, analyzing, and executing new and potential products, services, markets, and advertising opportunities
- Prepared reports that interpret customer behaviour, market opportunities, sales result, and potential competitors.
- Developed and conducted training modules with workshops for new employees in sales department.
- Developed training activities and references for new users for ERP system and OpenCart system.

Summary

Solutions-driven programmer with a three-year track record of commended performance in modular and object oriented programming. Well-versed in all phases of the software development lifecycle, with a strong working knowledge of algorithms and data structures.

EDUCATION

Diploma Of Computer Programming

Seneca College



09/2016 - 05/2018



Toronto, Ontario

Bachelor's Degree Of Statistics

National Taichung University Of Science And Technology



09/2009 - 06/2013



Taichung City, Taiwan

TECHNICAL PROFICENCY

Technical Skills

C, C++, Java, Android, Bash Scripting, VBA

Web Development

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, PHP, ReactJs, Angular, Node.is, Express.is

Database

MySQL, Oracle DB2, IAccess, MS Access, Postre SQL, MongoDB

Statistical Tools

SPSS, SAS, Minitab

Microsoft Certificate(MASTER)

Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, SharePoint, Outlook

Operating System

Unix/Linux, Mac OS, Windows

Artwork Design

Illustrator, Photoshop

Organization Management

ERP